squiglysplayhouse.com 2007-06-18

# Squigly's Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

In keeping with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we would like you to know how we handle the information we learn about you from your visit to Squigly's Playhouse. More information about COPPA can be found at the FTC's [Kidz Privacy page](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy/). The information we gather depends upon what you do when visiting our site.

1. | 

**Standard Activity Logging**

If you visit our site to play games, download activities or just read our pages, the following information about your visit is always recorded:

The name of the **domain** from which you access the Internet (e.g. webtv.net, aol.com, globalserve.net); the **date** and **time** you accessed our site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site (the **referrer** ).

The type of **browser** you are using (e.g. Netscape Navigator 4.7) and what **platform** (e.g. Power Macintosh).

This information is used to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site and gives us a better understanding of which activities our visitors enjoy doing while there.  

---|---  
2. | 

If you send us e-mail via the Joke, Brain Teaser, Brain Teaser of the Week or Writing Corner submission forms or the Write to Squigly form we record the following information (all fields are optional):

> Your **first name** is only recorded to accompany your submission as posted on our web site (e.g. a joke, story, etc.). Otherwise this information is discarded. You are never required to enter your last name and it will never be included with your posting.
> 
> Your **age** is recorded for two reasons: to accompany your submission; and for statistical purposes. It helps us to make age appropriate activities.
> 
> Your **country** is recorded for two reasons: to accompany your submission and for statistical purposes.

**Please note:** all submissions are screened and edited prior to being posted.  

3. | In addition to the fields noted above, our Write to Squigly form requests an **e-mail address** to allow us to reply to your questions. The address is not retained beyond the time required to provide such a response. The Write to Squigly form also collects information on the type of **browser** you are using (e.g. Netscape Navigator 4.7) and what **platform** (e.g. Power Macintosh, Windows). This information is used should you be inquiring about a technical difficulty.   
   
4. | 

Our Postcards require that two e-mail addresses be provided: the sender's and the recipient's. These addresses are used solely for the purpose of informing the recipient that they have been sent a card and the sender that the card has been picked up. The information is retained for 10 days in a secure location on our server and then deleted.  

5. | Our Tell a Friend feature similarly requires two e-mail addresses which are used to invite a friend to visit our site and to provide a confirmation letter to the one who made the invitation. The addresses are deleted as soon as the e-mails have been sent.  
   
6. | Our Quick Poll places a cookie on the user's computer for 24 hours to prevent "ballot stuffing." There is no personally identifying information contained in the cookie.  
   
7. | 

We have contracted with ValueClick, Burst!, Casale Media and Google Adsense to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick, Burst!, Casale and Google Adsense may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, Burst!, Casale Meida and Google Adsense please see their 's privacy policies by clicking on the appropriate link below. 

8. | 

Squigly also features games by Big Fish Games, Commission Junction and Regnow. These games have advanced features that may require registration to activate. Please read their [ ](http://store.gamehouse.com/privacy.html) privacy policies:

Once a particular theme has finished, all e-mail messages received during that theme are deleted. Submissions, as they appear in published form, are retained for potential future republication.

Once you have submitted something to Squigly's Playhouse, that submission becomes the property of Squigly's Playhouse but credit is given, wherever possible, to the submitter if and when the submission is published.

We want you to be very certain: **We will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us and we will never divulge any such information to any other party.**

Please be aware that, as a general rule, e-mail on the Internet is **not** a secure method of communication. Any e-mail you send or receive can be intercepted and read by another party.

If, at any time, your child has submitted a joke, brain teaser or writing corner submission that you do not want to be published, simply write or e-mail to the address below and the submission will be removed.

If you have any further questions or concerns please write to:

> Barb Willner  
>  Squigly's Playhouse  
>  P.O. Box 241  
>  Southampton, Ontario  
>  Canada N0H 2L0
> 
> 519-797-3475  
>  519-797-2874 (fax)  
>  Squigly@SquiglysPlayhouse.com

Games |   
Crafts |   
Jokes |   
Pencil Puzzles |   
Colouring |   
Brain Teasers |   
Writing Corner |   
Seasons & Holidays |   
Postcards  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| Home |  | **Privacy Policy** |  | Copyright © 1998-2005 Barb Willner. All rights reserved. |  | E-Mail Squigly |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
